Michał Kozłowski



Personal Data

Date of birth:

February 24, 1998

Address:

Wyspiańskiego 17 05-300 Mińsk Mazowiecki

Mob.:

884 852 588

michal@kozlovv.ski E-mail:

Languages

Polish: native

C1+ (CAE 500/2598/3) **English:**

German:

Software

MS Office:

Word, Excel, Access,

PowerPoint

Adobe:

Photoshop, Illustrator Premiere, InDesign

Corel:

Draw

Webdesign

Languages:

HTML5, CSS (SASS) JS (ES8, React + Next,

Redux)

Tools:

GIT, VSCode, Emmet, Webpack, GitHub, Yarn

Experience

8020 IM Solutions LTD

GitHub: github.com/kozlovvski

Portfolio: portfolio.kozlovv.ski/en

since November 2017 (remotely) Our company developes marketing campaigns for high-end services like cosmetic surgery. I am responsible mainly for creating the visual part of landing pages made in WordPress (in Thrive

Architect, landingi.com or Instapage page builders). I design blog posts and email campaigns for our clients and then try to increase their traffic conversion rate.

Volunteering

Warsaw School of Economics Students' Union

Board Member, Marketing Director

June 2018 to July 2019

I supervised marketing of an organization representing over 10.000 students enrolled at Warsaw School of Economics. My responsibility was to work with our graphic designers and make sure that our visual content is coherent and without any flaws. I conducted numerous workshops (in Adobe Illustrator and Photoshop) thusly training over 200 members of our organization. Also, I was responsible for dealing with any public affairs concerning our Union.

Adaptation Days 2018 Project Coordinator

May 2018 to June 2019

I coordinated a project for over 1.700 freshmen at Warsaw School of Economics. Our task was to make them feel like home since the very beginning of the academic year. We organized meetings with student organizations, corporate partners and conducted workshops in such topics as: useful points in university regulations; where to get help in any subject and basically how to graduate without unnecessary stress. With my core-team, I led a 150-strong team of volunteers who organized the whole event. Through 10 Corporate Partners we acquired and distributed over 30.000 PLN in budget. We managed to create a well-organized and secure event which University decided to include from now on in every following academic year.

Organization Member

since September 2017

Beside the experience listed above, I worked in marketing teams across 8 other projects. I created numerous rollups, ID cards, posters, web graphics or offers and reports for our Corporate Partners.

Polish Scouting Association National Board

December 2013 - June 2016

At a central level of an organization with over 100.000 members, I designed graphics for: websites, Facebook profiles, print on apparel or paper, video materials. As a part of ZPH360 - first scout internet television - I created Flash templates for live broadcasts (mainly lower thirds). I recorded and edited video materials to be used during our broadcasts. A few times I was a live broadcast producer - my task was to communicate with camera operators and choose which shots were broadcasted, everything during the most important organization events like 70th Anniversary of Monte Cassino Battle (an event in Italy). I also conducted workshops in in live broadcasting - we taught young scouts how to use cameras and broadcasting software, how broadcast studio is built etc.

Education

Warsaw School of Economics

since October 2017

Finance and Accounting, BA

About me

As my volunteering experience shows, I am a team player - I can both lead my team and follow someone else's command.. I love to learn new things and test myself in the new fields. I do not mind working under stress or deadline. When working on something, I do not like spending more time that it is necessary - I strive to optimize my activities and if I see a better way to complete a task, I try to implement it.

Beside design and webdevelopment, I am interested in long-distance running. This year I've completed my first marathon run and I plan to finish a 80-kilometer run in 2020.